Gorgeous Colombian on your arm, more
bling bling bling bracelets. I see you
player. I see. So, how long you've been
a drug dealer?
I mean, he's dating a Colombian.
He's wearing the uniform.
I called you a drug dealer last year?
HOLY I PICKED ON YOU LAST YEAR AND
I CALLED you a drug dealer and you're
still selling drugs?
DUDE.
I MUST BE A PROFESSIONAL.
WHAT KIND OF MUSIC you're into?
Rap?
Is that because you have
a big dick?
No?
He's got a little DICK AND HE'S PROUD OF
IT.
We should ask him what do you do?
You sell jewelry and you smuggle them
from what country?
And then what How did you find her?
Social media? What kind of jewelry have
you given her?
A lot? That makes sense with a small
dick.
WHAT? [screaming] HE STARTED IT.
FIRST OF ALL, you two look so hot
together. Let me just say that. And
thank you for being a good sport and
>> [cheering]
>> I love [applause] you.
Keep it up. And if you ever break up
with him, let me know your social media.
And my dick is even smaller than him.
Where are you originally from?
Syria? Are you Are you okay, buddy?
You're so serious.
You're my VIP guest. You're so serious.
He's like, "Axim, I'm here to hypnotize
you."
And sleep.
Whose idea was to come to my show.
Definitely yours, not him.
>> [applause and cheering]
>> He looks like he's held hostage.
>> [applause]
>> Habibi, if you laugh tonight, Turkish
food on me.
You got to laugh.
>> [applause]
>> And what was your name?
Your name?
He's thinking, "My name?"
I swear to God, I only do comedy. I
don't work for ICE.
Just comedy.
I promise you I won't tell the
government.
Tonight you go home, no problem.
Give me your name.
George?
This is what happens to us immigrants.
HE STILL DOESN'T TRUST. HE GOES, "The
first American name came to me." He
goes, "George."
George Muhammad Abdul
>> [applause]
>> Allahu Akbar.
Habibi, we love you. We want you to have
a good time, okay? We want you to laugh.
I want you to have a good time.
Otherwise, it's going to be the worst 2
hours of your life.
What do you do for a living? What's your
job?
>> Enjoy life.
>> Enjoy life. I can tell from your face.
>> [applause]
[cheering]
>> Number one comedian from Syria.
Number one comedian from Syria.
[cheering]
>> [applause]
>> How long has this been happening?
Three dates?
This is your third date? Oh my God. Who
bought the tickets?
He did? First of all, if you just met,
never sit in a front of a comedy show.
It could be your last time we see each
other.
And what's your name?
>> Ben.
>> Ben is such a smart guy.
Seriously, first of all, he picked up
the most beautiful girl in Houston with
such a big personality.
I mean the personality
>> [cheering]
>> is so magnificent.
I am so proud of this white guy.
I never thought in my life I'll see
George smile. As soon as the picture
came up
George approved.
It was like, I didn't enjoy life.
You guys just met, I'm assuming a few
days ago, yeah? Like a week ago, 10 days
ago, yeah? Recently?
>> Recently.
>> Recently. Just so everybody knows, these
tickets sold out very fast
months ago.
Before
>> [cheering]
>> So the question is, who did you
initially buy the ticket for?
>> [cheering]
>> Ben, I was joking.
I can feel your energy like you
Can I be honest with you? You're a kind
of guy that I can tell he's so nice and
honestly, I am rooting for you, too. If
I move to Houston, I want to have two
friends, Ben
and serial killer George.
So I can enjoy life.
You've been to the army, sir? What's
your name?
>> Tony.
>> Tony?
You look like you're from World War I.
How were the Germans? How bad ass they?
Tony, where you from?
>> Sicily.
>> Sicily, you're Italian?
>> Sicilian.
>> Oh, sorry. Sicilian. Damn, he's a bad
ass gangster Sicilian in the front. And
you married the Mexican lady, yeah? Oh,
you have a good taste, huh? And which
war were you involved in?
>> Iraq.
>> Iraq? As an American soldier?
So, you were raised here?
>> No.
>> No? You just left Italy, you're like,
"How you doing?
I'm Sicilian.
All right, I'm coming to help you all
out, okay? Send me a green card and a
Mexican lady.
COME ON, BUSH. LET ME IN.
AND THAT'S HOW Saddam went down.
The Sicilian walked in and Saddam woke
up with a horse head in his bed.
And what was your position in the army?
Did he just freeze? He's like, "Uh
What happened?
>> No, I was on different reconnaissance.
>> What's a reconnaissance?
>> You go out, you see, and then I
>> You go out, you see?
>> And then bring people in.
>> And then you bring people in?
You would go assess the situation and
you would go back and tell the captain
what you saw and based on your vision,
they would attack.
I heard you up a lot in Iraq.
A lot of unnecessary places got blown up
for no reason, man.
Of all THE SINGLE PEOPLE CLAP, I LIKE
THIS GUY. What's your name, buddy?
Habib? From?
>> Algeria.
>> Algeria. Wow, this guy intelligent,
Algeria. You know, they speak so many
languages, these Algerians. Please give
us, how many languages you speak?
>> I speak four.
>> Four languages? English, Arabic, French?
>> And Berber.
>> Berber?
Berber?
This guy thinks I'm stupid.
Berber, English, Arabic, Berber, Berber,
Berber.
>> WHAT DOES THIS MEAN?
WONDERFUL. AND WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN
AUSTIN?
I BUR bur I bur BUR ALL THE
TIME TRANSLATOR.
>> [laughter]
>> I TRANSLATE BUR BUR EVERYDAY.
And for the White House they they go bur
bur bur I go
I I know I know what they mean. I
translate.
What do you do for a living?
>> [screaming]
>> THIS IS WHY YOU'RE SINGLE. YOU CANNOT
COMMUNICATE.
HE GOES ON A DATE. WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> [screaming]
[laughter]
>> WHAT DO YOU DO?
HE GAVE UP.
YOU GIVE UP? YOU GOT TO GO HOME? YOU CAN
MASTURBATE.
>> [applause]
>> IS THAT WHAT YOU LIKE?
LONELY BY YOURSELF.
OH MY GOD. I'M GOING TO FIND YOU A HOT
BEAUTIFUL woman in Austin. Is that okay?
What's that?
What?
See you interrupt the show and you speak
Pakistani. I DON'T SPEAK PAKISTANI.
LOOK AT THE FILIPINO GUY.
YOU DON'T KNOW HIM?
Oh yeah, but but he seems like he's
going to pay for your drinks.
Oh that's not nice. You never do that.
See that's double standard.
girls can like publicly reject a man and
it's okay.
But men, we cannot reject you.
You take your shirt off, NIPPLE HAIR.
>> [laughter]
>> WE HAVE to go, oh, it's fantastic.
Oh, what a beautiful god-given nipple.
Oh, this nipple comes with frosting.
>> [applause]
>> YOU STILL TALKING?
>> [screaming]
[applause]
>> WHAT TENACITY.
But hairy nipples still persuading.